Ever since I was little, I've been having this same dream.
In it, I see this girl.
She's someone I've never met.
I'm in love with her.
The kind of deep love you can only feel after a lifetime.
And she loves me back just as much.
But in the end, something freaky happens.
The sky takes her back somehow.
And I wake up from the dream.
Unnerved and restless.
Hello, everyone.
Well, I'm Eishiro Sugata, resident genius.
This here is my assistant, pretty.
Hmm.
Look here.
There appears to be some type of anomalous hole orbiting the Earth.
Scientists around the world have been working together to try and solve the mystery of its origin.
They've even dropped monitoring devices into the anomaly, but haven't settled on any logical conclusion.
But you see, their hypotheses are flawed because they are grounded in reality.
As I'm sure you're aware, Columbus, who discovered the Americas, was able to stand an egg on its end by simply thinking outside of the box.
This story illustrates that no one believes in the unreal until they see it for themselves.
It's the nature of people.
It's similar to the world beneath a girl's skirt.
Something truly a mystery.
But I have the ability to see.
I can see the key words that connect everything.
A whole new world.
Now, the next issue is what makes up this whole new world.
Speaking metaphorically, you could say that under the girl's skirt...
Tomo, come on!
Would you get up already?
We're gonna be late for school.
Just five more minutes.
For crying out loud, get up!
You know, I hear that's a good sign.
When the flag's full of mass first thing in the morning.
Come on.
No!
At least drink some milk before we head out.
Yeah, thanks.
And your tie's all messed up.
It doesn't matter how old you get, you still act like a child.
All right, let's get going.
We live in Sorami City.
It's a small town with a population of about 7,000.
Completely surrounded by mountains.
It's nice.
The town isn't known for anything in particular.
If it was, it'd be the smile of the old farmer's face.
Or maybe the humongous 400-year-old cherry blossom tree
that sits on that hill right outside of town.
Reinforcing this sense of isolation...
Everyone always complains about how there's nothing to do here.
But I like it.
It's my kind of place.
My motto is this.
Peace and quiet is the only way to live.
I like to watch TV, eat, take a nap during class.
The most perfect thing you can ask for
is just a thread of peace and quiet running through your life.
Wouldn't you agree?
Save me.
The sky has me in its grip.
Tomo!
Wake up!
Tomoki!
Class is over if you hadn't noticed!
You had the dream again, didn't you?
Oh, great.
Am I crying?
Look, Tomoki.
You've been having that dream ever since you were a little kid.
Think maybe you should see a doctor about it or something?
It's just some stupid dream.
It's not like it's ruining my life or anything.
Okay.
Wait, I have an idea.
What if we run it by Sugata, see what he thinks?
No freaking way.
I don't want to get wrapped up with some dude
who just looks like he attracts trouble.
Hey, everyone come quick.
Some moron's about to jump off the roof.
Jump off the roof?
The wind is good today,
although I'm not exactly happy with the direction it's blowing.
But it won't be a problem for takeoff.
Don't do it!
You're in sight!
You'll die!
Oh, hello there, Miss President.
Good morning.
Um, is someone going to jump off the roof?
Take a look.
What?
Sugata!
Shouldn't you be trying to stop him?
I could ask him to come down, but he won't listen.
I'll worry about it after he falls.
Could you be more irresponsible?
I mean, you're student council president.
You've got to do something.
If you're talking about insurance,
I already bought a whole lot of it.
Several million worth of life insurance, to be exact.
Wow, that's a lot.
Don't you stand there acting all impressed?
Come on, Prez.
Aren't you two like childhood friends or something?
Shouldn't you show the tiniest bit of consideration?
Are you suggesting I'm not worried about him in the slightest?
No, that's not...
Are you suggesting I believe it might not be such a bad thing
to watch my dear friend plummet to his death
with a big smile spread across my face
as a cherry blossoms bloom in the background?
I didn't say that.
And are you suggesting I'm even considering
the remote possibility that after I've made my claim
on the insurance, I'll travel the world
on the finest luxury cruise liner
while I mourn my friend's untimely passing?
Are you?
What do you think?
Are you sure you want that answer?
No.
He jumped.
Be careful!
Oh.
So, you want to head back?
Hang on, Tomo.
What about your dream?
I am so not talking to that guy.
What are you talking about?
Tomo's just being stupid.
He wants to ask Sugata some questions.
We heard he's in the know regarding out there kinds of things.
You'd be right about that.
He's creepy, perverted beyond belief,
weird beyond comprehension,
and without a doubt,
the freakiest for a guy I know of.
But he's dependable for what you need.
Dependably nuts?
Well, who the hell else are we going to ask?
I mean, you refuse to go see a professional.
I just want to live in peace and quiet.
Fine, then.
Have it your way, jackass.
I understand every word of your concerns.
Many intelligent people believe dreams to be electrical signals
your brain sends out when processing memories.
In other words,
your desires or your memories
become your dreams during your sleep.
Okay.
But that's nothing more than a hypothesis grounded in reality,
and you can't explain the unreal using real terms.
Look at this.
No, not that.
You know what that is?
The black spot?
No.
Of course you don't.
What now?
Because you've already concluded you don't know.
There are scientists who've spent years researching this
and have yet to figure out the slightest thing about it.
But I understand it.
I know exactly what the true nature is behind this hole.
And of course, I also know what your dream means.
Both of them are part of a whole new world.
Such fools in the scientific community.
Something with this much mass,
this much displacement,
it can't be anything but a whole new world
floating over there.
This recurring dream you've been having
is also connected to this whole new world.
Have faith in me,
and I will unlock the mystery of this dream of yours.
That's great.
At precisely midnight tonight,
this whole new world of which I speak
will fly over this town.
Do you mind if I come check it out?
Sounds just fine.
This is bad.
I can already hear it.
The sound of my beautiful peace and quiet
being torn apart at the seams.
The cherry blossom tree
next to the shrine at midnight.
We're going to see this together.
I'm sorry,
but my mother told me
I can't stay out past midnight tonight.
Apologies.
Mikuko needs me tonight.
It doesn't look like I'll be able to join you.
To everyone who said
they'd come up here with me tonight,
thanks a lot.
I'm looking around,
and guess what?
No one.
Sincerely, Tomaki.
To hell with this.
I'm out of here.
Oh, it's Sugata.
Hey, what's up, weirdo?
Get the hell out of there.
I just did another pass
over the most recent data,
and something odd is going on.
I'm heading over the...
What?
You're breaking up.
I can't hear.
The hole is moving.
What?
You're in danger.
Oh, no.
It's a person.
No.
It's not a person.
A person doesn't have...
A person doesn't have wings.
Don't think about how weird this is.
The whole mess just stinks of trouble.
Run away!
What the hell is happening?
It should be fine.
I'm sure of it.
The chick fell out of the freaking sky
without a scratch on her.
I'm not getting involved.
No way.
Peace and quiet is the best.
That's my motto,
and I'm sticking to it.
That's it.
That's what I say.
Those are the words I live by.
Oh, damn it!
Oh, man.
All I want is to live in peace.
After this, I'm gonna go home, watch TV,
and pass the hell out.
Ah...
Ah!
Ah.
Begin imprinting process.
It is a pleasure to meet you, I am a pet class Angeloid, my purpose is to fulfill your every
want and desire. You are my master. Hey Tomo, I'm on cleaning duty today so I'm gonna head off to school. Get your ass out of bed so you're not late. Good morning, master.
Master, please make a command. Give me any order that will please you. Anything you desire. Angeloids were created for the sole purpose of bringing our master's pleasure. It is all we know.
So whatever I want. Yes. You're... My what? Well, how about a bunch of cash? You are requesting a... That was almost weird. I was about to get my freak on with an alien creature from space or wherever. What's wrong with my head? Yeah, duh. If I had that much money, I could buy anything I wanted in the whole world. Initiating transfer.
You're screwing with my head. What is that card thingy? Let me see it. Hand it over.
In your language, this card would be known as a teleportation device.
Teleportation? I hear your request and all I need to do is order the required materials from the synapse. What's the synapse?
I have no stored information regarding the synapse. Those databanks are clear. After all, I have only just awoken so I am void of much data.
I am a pet class, Angeloid. My type is Alpha, Icarus. I was manufactured by the synapse for you.
I have no stored information regarding the synapse.
I have no stored information regarding the synapse. Those databanks are clear.
After all, I have only just awoken so I am void of much data. I am a pet class, Angeloid. My type is Alpha, Icarus. I was manufactured by the synapse for you. For your sole pleasure.
I don't care about all that noise. Too confusing. What I want to know is what else can you do?
Anything.
Anything?
Correct.
Come on.
Oh, these stupid things have grown again, haven't they? There's no point in them being this big.
Oh, yeah. The invisible kicks ass.
Master, why are we here?
Living a man's dream, Icarus. That's what we're doing.
Something about men? Everything comes down to our libidos. Oh, and food.
Huh.
Now, let's mess with her some.
That was awesome. I can't believe I actually got her.
Master, please explain.
That, my good Icarus, was punishment.
Punishment for the vicious girl who's always karate chopping me with her stupid hands.
It was punishment.
Okay, Icarus. Time for the next one.
Transport!
Time...
Stop!
Master?
Yes! Everywhere I want to go is mine. The world is mine for the taking.
Oh.
Let's keep moving!
I know, but that's what I told them.
Sure, I did, guys.
Yeah!
I am king of the world!
Your panties are mine!
How is your dinner, Master?
It's lighting up my taste buds.
But what is this stuff anyway? I've never had it before.
The card summoned a quantum food changer which transformed the air in such a way...
Forget about it. That crap's way over my head.
Do you have any further commands, Master?
Not right now.
Except maybe... you stripping?
Alright.
No, no! Reel that in! Seriously!
I was just kidding! It was a joke! Cancel that order!
I cannot cancel orders.
I was not given capacity for that function.
Do you have any further orders, Foreman?
No, no! Nothing I can think of!
In fact, I'm exhausted.
We're done for today.
We can just pick up the whole thing where we left off tomorrow.
What do you say?
That said, I'm happy I've gotten to do everything I wanted to.
I guess the only thing left on my list is to take over the world.
Tomo! Time to wake up!
Why were you in school yesterday, dumbass?
The teacher was pissed!
You're in so much trouble today!
Open up the freakin' door!
I heard you. Ease up!
What are you...
What?
Hey, uh...
Sahara?
What the heck?
World domination will be complete momentarily, Master.
What?
I activated a world domination program while you slept.
Don't tell me!
According to my research, not a single human on planet Earth would recognize you as their supreme ruler.
It therefore seems the program determined the best course of action was to erase all other humans on the planet from existence.
Wait, every other human being on the planet?
Correct.
Can you cancel that?
I cannot.
I was not given capacity for that function.
I can't believe this.
I only wanted a normal life.
A peaceful one.
And look at what I get!
The exact opposite!
Is it?
Is there really no one left on the entire planet?
I apologize, Master.
I interpreted your statement as an order.
What do you wish now?
Would it remedy the situation if I destroy myself?
Yeah.
I guess that'd make things a little better.
I've had enough of this BS.
Yes, Master.
Master?
I was just kidding.
It's just a joke, you know?
Go ahead and cancel that last order, okay?
I cannot cancel an order.
Why the hell not?
You haven't done a single thing wrong.
You've just been following every stupid order I've spit out.
Come on, there's no reason for you to die.
I was not given capacity for that function.
I'm thanking you!
You have to help me.
Everyone left because of me.
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
Don't leave me here all alone.
I'm on my knees.
Cancel that order.
Stay.
Stay with me, please.
I will, Master.
I wish this whole mess was nothing but one bad nightmare.
Keep your angel treasure.
And never part with her.
Not ever.
Hey, Tomo!
I'm on cleaning duty today so I'm gonna head off to school!
Get your ass out of bed!
This whole mess was nothing but one bad nightmare.
Keep your angel. Treasure of me.
And never part with her. Not ever.
Hey, Tomo! I'm on cleaning duty today, so I'm gonna head off to school!
Was that some kind of tripped-out dream or what? I feel all dizzy.
Whoa, man. I can't even tell which way is up. What's my problem?
Are you well this morning, Master?
You!
You wished everything was nothing more than a nightmare, so I activated a program.
Then made it all into a dream and returned the world to normal.
You can actually do that?
Did I do bad?
Hell no! You did a great thing! You're the best ever!
But to be honest, I'm more tired than I've ever been.
Pardon me, Master.
Is this something you want to stay as part of your dream as well?
Hmm? Is what something?
You told me to stay with you. Then you said you wanted everything to change back.
Would it be better if I remained a part of your dream state?
I think you should do whatever you want, Icarus.
Master?
I do not understand.
Do I have to explain everything?
No, Master.
I say this all the time, but the only thing I want in this world is to live a normal, peaceful life.
Except there's this chick with a vicious karate chop who's always out to get me.
And some freak boy who thinks he can fly stressing me out.
And last but certainly not least, I got Icarus.
The girl who fell from the sky.
And that's how this whole thing began.
These are days I don't think I'll ever forget.
Also, like.
There is a piece we got so far from, classified as purification as functions.
To be fair, look.
Sookie I swear this well.
Okay, we heard it.
Thank you.